<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.
  
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!--
Copyright 2006 Curam Software Ltd.                               
All rights reserved.                                              
This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam 
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information"). You shall not disclose  
such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance with 
the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.                                                            
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_DELETE_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">This determination package has been released and cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_COMBINATION_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">This Age range overlaps with another determination package with this Gender and Product within this determination configuration.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_DELETED">
    <locale language="en">The determination configuration to which you are trying to add this determination package has been deleted.Therefore this determination package cannot be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_AGE_MUST_INTEGER">
    <locale language="en">Age Should be in Integer.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_DEFAULT_COMBINATION_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">There can only be one determination package with no Product, Min Age, Max Age or Gender specified for each determination configuration.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_UNIQUE_COMBINATION_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">Each Gender, Age range and Product combination for a determination package must be unique for that determination configuration.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_NAME_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Name must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_XRV_NAME_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A determination package with this Name already exists.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_MINAGE_MAXAGE_COMBINATION_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The Maximum Age should be greater than or equal to the Minimum Age.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_MINAGE_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">If entered the Minimum Age should be zero or greater.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE_MAXAGE_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">If entered the Maximum Age should be zero or greater.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_CANCELLED">
    <locale language="en">The determination to which you are trying to add this determination package has been deleted. Therefore this determination package cannot be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">This version has been released and cannot be modified. To modify the determination package you must first create a new version.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DELETE_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_HAS_QUESTIONNAIRES">
    <locale language="en">This determination package version has associated questionnaires and cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DELETE_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_HAS_DMS">
    <locale language="en">This determination package version has associated decision matrices and cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATIONCONFIGURATION_ENDDATE_EARLIER_THAN_CURRENTBUSINESSDATE">
    <locale language="en">This determination package cannot be released as the end date of the determination configuration %1d is earlier than current date.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_INEDIT">
    <locale language="en">A new determination package version cannot be created because the latest version is In Edit.\n You must Release or Delete the latest version before creating a new version.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_IN_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">The determination package has been released and a new questionnaire cannot be added.You must create a new version of the determination package to add a new questionnaire.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_NOT_RELEASED_NO_QUESTIONNAIRE">
    <locale language="en">No questionnaire has been associated with this determination package.Create and release a questionnaire for this determination package and then try again.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_NOT_RELEASED_QUESTIONNAIRE_IN_EDIT">
    <locale language="en">A questionnaire associated with this determination package is In Edit. Please Release or Delete the In Edit version of this questionnaire and try again.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED_NO_MATRICES">
    <locale language="en">No decision matrix has been associated with this determination package.Create and release a decision matrix for this determination package and then try again.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED_MATRICES_IN_EDIT">
    <locale language="en">A decision matrix associated with this determination package is In Edit. Please Release or Delete the In Edit version of this decision matrix and try again.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED_DETERMINATION_START_DATE_IN_FUTURE">
    <locale language="en">This determination package cannot be released as the Start Date of the determination configuration %1d is in the future.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_IS_ALREADY_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">This determination package has already been released.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIRE_ALREADY_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire is already associated with this determination package version.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIRE_CANNOT_REMOVE_PACKAGE_INEDIT">
    <locale language="en">The determination package has been released and cannot be modified. You must create a new version of the determination package to remove a questionnaire.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DP_ALREADY_RELEASED_MATRIX_CANNOT_BE_ADDED">
    <locale language="en">The determination package has been released and a new decision matrix cannot be added. You must create a new version of the determination package to add a new decision matrix.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_RELEASED_DELETE_MATRIX">
    <locale language="en">This determination package has been released and cannot be modified. To remove the decision matrix a new In Edit version of the package must be created. </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_EXISTS_FOR_THIS_DETERMINATIONCONFIGURATION_WITH_OPTIONAL_CRITERIA_AGE">
    <locale language="en">A determination package already exists for this determination configuration with the optional criteria Age. Another determination package cannot be created with a different optional criteria. </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_EXISTS_FOR_THIS_DETERMINATIONCONFIGURATION_WITH_OPTIONAL_CRITERIA_GENDER">
    <locale language="en">A determination package already exists for this determination configuration with the optional criteria Gender. Another determination package cannot be created with a different optional criteria. </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_EXISTS_FOR_THIS_DETERMINATIONCONFIGURATION_WITH_OPTIONAL_CRITERIA_FOR_PRODUCT_GENDER">
    <locale language="en">A determination package already exists on this determination configuration for this product with the optional criteria Gender. Another determination package cannot be created for this product with a different optional criteria. </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_DETERMINATION_PACKAGE_EXISTS_FOR_THIS_DETERMINATIONCONFIGURATION_WITH_OPTIONAL_CRITERIA_FOR_PRODUCT_AGE">
    <locale language="en">A determination package already exists on this determination configuration for this product with the optional criteria Age. Another determination package cannot be created for this product with a different optional criteria. </locale>
  </message>
</messages>