<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.
  
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!--
Copyright 2006 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.
This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information"). You shall not disclose
such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance with
the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_CANCELLED_ASSESSMENT_CANNOT_CANCELLED">
    <locale language="en">This assessment may not be canceled as it has already been canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This assessment may not be cancelled as it has already been cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_COMPLETED_ASSESSMENT_CANNOT_CANCELLED">
    <locale language="en">This assessment may not be canceled as it has already been completed.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This assessment may not be cancelled as it has already been completed.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_DATE_BEFORE_DC_STARTDATE">
    <locale language="en">The assessment date entered is before the start date of the determination %1d. Please enter a new assessment date or select a new assessment.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_DATE_AFTER_DC_ENDDATE">
    <locale language="en">The assessment date entered is after the end date of the determination %1d. Please enter a new assessment date.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_DP_NO_COC">
    <locale language="en">There are no decision making criteria available for this Assessment for the Assessment Date entered. Please enter a new Assessment Date or select a different Assessment.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_DP_COC">
    <locale language="en">There are no decision making criteria available for the Determination in this Assessment.  Please enter a new Assessment Date or select a different Assessment.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_DETERMINATION">
    <locale language="en">The selected assessment does not have a determination associated to it.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_CANCELLED_ASSESSMENT_CANNOT_COMPLETE">
    <locale language="en">This assessment may not be completed as it has already been canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This assessment may not be completed as it has already been cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_COMPLETED_ASSESSMENT_CANNOT_COMPLETE">
    <locale language="en">This assessment may not be completed as it has already been completed.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_CANCELLED__CANNOT_DO_CREATE_DECISION">
    <locale language="en">Decisions cannot be created as this assessment has already been canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Decisions cannot be created as this assessment has already been cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_STATUS_COMPLETED_CANNOT_DO_CREATE_DECISION">
    <locale language="en">Decisions cannot be created as this assessment has already been completed.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_DP_FOR_CLONE_ASSESSMENT">
    <locale language="en">'There are no decision making criteria available for this Determination for this Effective Date. Please enter a new Effective Date or select Cancel to exit'.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_EFFECTIVE_DATE_FOR_CLONE_ASSESSMENT">
    <locale language="en">'Effective Date' must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_NO_ASSOCIATION_FOR_ASSESSMENT_DATE">
    <locale language="en">The assessment date entered is not valid as there is no association to this case type on this date. The association periods are as follows:%1s.Please enter a new assessment date or select a new assessment.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSESSMENT_MULTIPLE_DC_FOR_ASSESSMENT_DATE">
    <locale language="en">The assessment has more than one determination. Please select a new assessment.</locale>
  </message>
</messages>
