<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.
  
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!--
Copyright 2006 Curam Software Ltd.                               
All rights reserved.                                              
This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam 
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information"). You shall not disclose  
such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance with 
the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.                                                            
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_NAME_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Questionnaire Name must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_TYPE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Questionnaire type must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_NAME_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A questionnaire with this Name already exists.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_STATUS_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire has been released and cannot be modified. To modify the questionnaire a new In Edit version must be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_DELETE_STATUS_RELEASED">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire has been released and cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_NEW_VERSION_STATUS_INEDIT">
    <locale language="en">There is currently an In Edit version of this questionnaire. This must be released or deleted before a new version can be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_RELEASE_FOR_RELEASED_QUESTIONNAIRE">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire version has already been released. To release a new version an In Edit version must be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_RELEASE_QUESTIONNAIRE_TP_INEDIT">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire Version cannot be released as there is an In Edit typical picture associated with it. The associated In Edit typical picture must be released or deleted before this questionnaire version can be released.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_REMOVE_TP_FOR_INEDIT_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire has been released and cannot be modified. To remove the typical picture a new In Edit version of the questionnaire must be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_ENT_RELEASED_SYNC">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire has been released and therefore associated typical pictures cannot be synchronized.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_XRV_SYNC_NO_TP">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire has no typical pictures and cannot be synchronized.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_STATUS_RELEASED_QUESTIONS_EDIT">
    <locale language="en">This version has been released and cannot be modified. To modify the questionnaire you must first create a new In Edit version.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_ASSOCIATED_TO_RELEASED_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE">
    <locale language="en">There is a released version of a Determination Package which includes this script. Changing the script will have implications for Change of Circumstances and Clone functions; the previous answers cannot be pre-populated due to this change in the script.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_DELETE_STATUS_RELEASED_AND_ASSOCIATED_TO_DETERMINATIONPACKAGE">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire is released and associated to a determination package and therefore cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_DELETE_QUESTION_GROUP_ASSOCIATED_TO_OTHER_SCRIPTS">
    <locale language="en">This question script contains question groups which are used by other question scripts, it cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_DELETE_NOT_LATEST_VERSION">
    <locale language="en">This is not the latest questionnaire version, it cannot be deleted.</locale>
  </message>


  <!--IEG2 migration work-->
  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_FV_RELEASE_QUESTIONNAIRE_VERSION_ASSOCIATED_TO_INEDIT_QUESTIONNAIRE">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire version has links to another 'In Edit' questionnaire version. That questionnaire version must be released before releasing this questionnaire version.</locale>
  </message>


  <message name="ERR_QUESTIONNAIREVERSION_ASSOCIATED_TO_RELEASED_QUESTIONNAIRE">
    <locale language="en">This questionnaire is linked to other released questionnaires. If you wish these other questionnaires to use the new version of this questionnaire, they should be updated to refer to this new questionnaire version.</locale>
  </message>


</messages>
