<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.
  
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!--
Copyright 2007 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_THIRD_PARTY_NOT_SELECTED">
    <locale language="en">A third party must be selected or entered before a request can be saved.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_ONLY_ONE_THIRD_PARTY_SHOULD_BE_SELECTED">
    <locale language="en">Only one Third Party can be entered. Please select a Third Party Participant, or search for a registered Third Party, or enter details for an unregistered Third Party.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_UNSENT_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_ALREADY_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">A third party request that has not yet been sent already exists for this Third Party. The unsent request should be sent or canceled before a new request to this person can be created.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A third party request that has not yet been sent already exists for this Third Party. The unsent request should be sent or cancelled before a new request to this person can be created.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_THIRD_PARTY_TYPE_IS_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Third Party Type needs to be selected.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_NO_QUESTION_SELECTED">
    <locale language="en">Questions must be selected before the request can be saved.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_QUESTION_NOT_ADDED">
    <locale language="en">Questions have not been added to the request. Please add questions before sending the request.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_CANCEL_SENT">
    <locale language="en">This third party request has been sent and cannot be canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This third party request has been sent and cannot be cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_CANCEL_ANSWER_RECD">
    <locale language="en">Answers have been received for this third party request and it cannot be canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Answers have been received for this third party request and it cannot be cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_ANSWER_NO_ANSWERS_RECORDED">
    <locale language="en">No answers have been recorded for this third party request, answers must be entered before you can save.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_ANSWER_DATE_BFR_REQUEST">
    <locale language="en">The Date Received entered is before the date the third party answers were requested. Please check the date and re-enter.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_ANSWER_DATE_FUTURE">
    <locale language="en">The Date Received entered is a date in the future. Please check the date and re-enter.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_ANSWER_NO_ANSWERS_UPDATED">
    <locale language="en">No answers have been updated for this third party request, answers must be updated before you can save.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_NO_ALIAS_QUESTIONS">
    <locale language="en">There are no question aliases for this Third Party Type.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_THIRD_PARTY_REQUEST_CLAIMANT_CANNOT_BE_SELECTED_AS_THIRD_PARTY">
    <locale language="en">Claimant cannot be selected as a Third Party.</locale>
  </message>
</messages>
