<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2013. All Rights Reserved.
 
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->  
<!-- 
Copyright 2011 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.workflow.message">

  <!-- Activity Allocation Messages -->
  <message name="ID_CER_RULE_SET_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The CER rule set "%1s" associated with the allocation strategy can no longer be found.</locale>
    <cause>The CER rule set specified as part of the allocation strategy can no longer be found.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the name of the rule set is correct and that it exists on the system.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A CER class attribute must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>No CER class attribute was specified.</cause>
    <action>Ensure a valid CER class attribute is specified.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_RULESET_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The CER rule set name must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The CER rule set name has not been specified.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid CER rule set name.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_RULE_CLASS_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The CER rule class name must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The CER rule class name has not been specified.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid CER rule class name.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_INVALID_CER_RULE_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules class attribute "%1s" is not valid.</locale>
    <cause>The CER rules class attribute identifier is invalid.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER rules class attribute identifier is valid.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_WDO_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_ASSIGNABLE_TO_CER_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The workflow data object attribute "%1s" is not assignable to the CER class attribute "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The WDO attribute is not assignable to the CER class attribute.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the types of the WDO attribute and associated CER class attributes are compatible.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_MAPPING_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A mapping already exists for the CER class attribute "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>The mapping already exists and cannot be duplicated.</cause>
    <action>Make sure the mapping name is unique.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_RULE_SETS_AVAILABLE_FOR_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">There are no CER rule sets available for mapping.</locale>
    <cause>There are no CER rule sets available for creating allocation strategy mappings.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the system contains CER rule sets that may be used for workflow allocation strategy mappings.</action>
  </message>   
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_RULES_CLASSES_AVAILABLE_FOR_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">There are no CER rules classes available for mapping in the CER rule set "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>There are no CER rules classes available in the specified CER rule set that can be used to create allocation strategy input mappings.</cause>
    <action>Pick a CER rule set that contains rules classes that be used for input mappings.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_RULES_CLASS_ATTRIBUTES_AVAILABLE_FOR_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">There are no attributes available for mapping in the CER rules class "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>There are no attributes available for mapping to in the specified CER rules class.</cause>
    <action>Pick a CER rules class that contains attributes that may be used in mappings for the specified allocation strategy.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_CER_PRIMARY_RULES_CLASSES_AVAILABLE">
    <locale language="en">There are no CER rules classes available for the return mapping in the CER rule set "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>There are no CER rules classes available in the specified CER rule set that can be used to create the return mapping. Such CER classes must have an attribute called targets.</cause>
    <action>A CER rule set must be chosen that contains a class that may be specified as the primary CER rules class for the allocation strategy.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_PRIMARY_RULES_CLASS_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The name of the CER primary rules class must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The name of the CER primary rules class has not been specified.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid name for the CER primary rules class to allow the mapping to be created.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_PRIMARY_RULES_CLASS_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules class named "%1s" specified as the primary rule class cannot be found in the CER rule set "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The specified CER primary rules class cannot be found in the specified CER rule set.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER primary rules class name that has been specified is correct. If not, then specify another name or add the CER rules class.</action>
  </message>
   <message name="ID_CER_RULES_CLASS_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules class named "%1s" cannot be found in the CER rule set "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The specified CER rules class cannot be found in the specified CER rule set.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER rules class name that has been specified is correct. If not, then specify another name or add the CER rules class.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULES_PRIMARY_CLASS_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules primary class "%1s" is invalid as it must extend the abstract work allocation targets rules class "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The CER rules primary class must extend an abstract workflow allocation targets class that is delivered.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER rules class specified as the primary class extends the specified class or choose another class.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULES_OTHER_CLASS_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules non primary class "%1s" is invalid as it must extend the abstract work allocation targets rules class "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The CER rules non primary class must extend an abstract workflow allocation targets class that is delivered.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER rules class specified as the non primary class extends the specified class or choose another class.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULES_PRIMARY_CLASS_NO_TARGETS_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The CER rules primary class "%1s" must contain an attribute called "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The CER rules primary class must contain a targets attribute as this is the attribute that the workflow engine uses to get the list of allocation targets.</cause>
    <action>Either add a targets attribute to the CER primary rules class or choose another CER rules class to act as the primary class.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_CER_RULES_CLASS_INPUT_MAPPING_WDO_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The workflow data object attribute "%1s" used in an allocation strategy CER rules class input mapping is not valid.</locale>
    <cause>The WDO attribute that has been specified in a CER rules class input mapping is invalid.</cause>
    <action>A valid WDO attribute must be specified for the CER rules class input mapping.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_CER_RULES_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_USED_IN_INPUT_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">The type of the CER rules class attribute "%1s" used in an allocation strategy CER rules class input mapping is not valid.</locale>
    <cause>The type of the CER class attribute that has been specified in a CER rules class input mapping is invalid.</cause>
    <action>A type of the CER class attribute for the CER rules class input mapping must be valid.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DUPLICATE_CER_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">A duplicate allocation strategy CER class input mapping exists for the CER class attribute "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>Duplicate mappings exist for the specified CER class attributes.</cause>
    <action>The mappings must be changed to ensure that there are no duplicates specified.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_NO_LOCAL_ATTRIBUTE_FOR_MAPPING_CER_CLASS_ON_PRIMARY_CLASS">
    <locale language="en">The primary CER rules class "%1s" does not contain a local attribute of the correct type for the CER class "%2s" which is used in the allocation strategy CER class mappings. This is required to allow an instance of the CER class to be set at run time.</locale>
    <cause>The CER rules primary class does not contain a local attribute of the correct type for one of the rules classes used in the allocation strategy metadata mappings.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the specified primary rules class contains a local attribute of the correct type for each CER rules class that is used in the CER class metadata mappings for an allocation strategy.</action>
  </message>  
   <message name="ID_CER_RULES_CLASS_SPECIFIED_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_USED_IN_INPUT_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">The specified attribute "%2s" of the CER rules class "%1s" is not used in an allocation strategy CER rules class input mapping. The input mappings need to be refreshed.</locale>
    <cause>The specified attribute of the CER rules class is not used in an allocation strategy CER rules class input mapping.</cause>
    <action>A valid CER class attribute must be contained in the CER rules class input mapping.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULES_CLASS_IN_MAPPING_NOT_IN_SPECIFIED_RULESET">
    <locale language="en">The specified CER rule class "%1s" in the input mappings is not in the actual specified rule set "%2s". The input mappings need to be refreshed.</locale>
    <cause>The specified CER rule class in the input mappings is not in the actual specified rule set.</cause>
    <action>The invalid CER rule class should be remnoved from the CER rules class input mapping.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULES_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_IN_MAPPING_NOT_IN_SPECIFIED_RULECLASS">  
    <locale language="en">The CER rule class attribute "%1s" used in the allocation strategy input mappings does not exist in the CER Rule class "%2s". The input mapping should be refreshed.</locale>
    <cause>The specified CER rule class attribute is not in the actual specified rule class.</cause>
    <action>The invalid CER rule class attribute should be remnoved from the CER rules class input mapping.</action>
  </message>
  <!-- End of Activity Allocation Messages -->
  <message name="ID_CANNOT_DELETE_DEFAULT_PROCESS_DISPLAY_NAME">
    <locale language="en">The default display name cannot be deleted.</locale>
    <cause>An attempt was made to delete the default display name for the process.</cause>
    <action>The default display name text cannot be deleted.</action>
  </message> 
  <message name="ID_PROCESS_DISPLAY_NAME_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A workflow process definition with display name "%1s" already exists.</locale>
    <cause>A workflow process with that display name already exists.</cause>
    <action>Give the process a unique display name.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_PROCESS_DISPLAY_NAME_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A process display name must be specified for process "%1s".</locale>
    <cause>A workflow process display name must be specified, it is either null or empty.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the display name is not null or empty.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_PROCESS_DISPLAY_NAME_EXCEEDS_ALLOWED_LENGTH">
    <locale language="en">The length of the display name of process "%1s" is "%2n". The maximum allowed length is "%3n".</locale>
    <cause>The length of the workflow process name cannot exceed the allowed length.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the length of the workflow process name is within the allowed limits.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ERROR_RETRIEVING_LOCALIZED_PROCESS_DISPLAY_NAME">
    <locale language="en">Could not retrieve the localized process display name for the process. Reason: %1s</locale>
    <cause>The specified error occurred retrieving the localized process display name from the process definition metadata.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the metadata contains the correct process display name information, including a display name for the default locale.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_CER_RULE_CLASS_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_LIST_OF_CER_RULE_CLASSES">  
    <locale language="en">The CER rule class attribute named "%1s" has not been defined as a list and therefore does not contain a list of the CER rule class named "%2s".</locale>
    <cause>The CER rule class attribute has not been defined as a list and therefore does not contain a list of the CER rule class.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER rule class attribute represents a list of the specified rule classes.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_WDO_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_LIST_WDO">  
    <locale language="en">The workflow data object attribute "%1s" cannot be mapped to the CER rule class list attribute "%2s", as this workflow data object is not a list workflow data object.</locale>
    <cause>The workflow data object attribute cannot be mapped to the CER rule class list attribute, as this workflow data object is not a list workflow data object.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the workflow data object attribute is a list WDO.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_WDO_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_LIST_WDO_FOR_LOOP_ACTIVITY">
    <locale language="en">The specified workflow data object "%1s" cannot be used in this mapping as the associated activity is in a loop.</locale>
    <cause>The specified workflow data object cannot be used in this mapping as the associated activity is is in a loop.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the workflow data object attribute is a list WDO format for a loop activity.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_WDO_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_LIST_WDO_FOR_PARALLEL_ACTIVITY">
    <locale language="en">The indexed list workflow data object attribute, "%1s", cannot be mapped to this CER class attribute as this activity is parallel activity.</locale>
    <cause>The indexed list workflow data object attribute, cannot be mapped to this CER class attriute as this activity is parallel activity.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the workflow data object attribute is a list WDO format for a parallel activity.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULE_CLASS_MAPPING_MISSING_SOURCE_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The CER class attribute "%1s" is not mapped to a WDO attribute.</locale>
    <cause>The CER class attribute is not mapped to a WDO attribute.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the CER class attribute is mapped to a WDO attribute.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CER_RULE_CLASS_MAPPING_MISSING_TARGET_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">The WDO attribute "%1s" is not mapped to a CER class attribute.</locale>
    <cause>The WDO attribute is not mapped to a CER class attribute.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the WDO attribute is mapped to a CER class attribute.</action>
  </message>
</messages>