<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012,2017. All Rights Reserved.
 
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->  
<messages package="curam.intelligentevidencegathering.message">
  <!-- Editor script validation messages -->
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_IDENTIFIER_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The identifier must be specified for the script.</locale>
    <cause>The identifier has not been specified for the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify an identifier for the script.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The script ID must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The ID has not been specified for the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for the script.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_VERSION_NUMBER_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The script version number must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The script version number has not been specified for the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a script version number for the script.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_TYPE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The script type must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The type has not been specified for the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a type for the script.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_CONTAINS_NO_PAGES">
    <locale language="en">The script does not contain any pages.</locale>
    <cause>The script currently does not contain any pages.</cause>
    <action>Define one or more pages for the script.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_CONTAINS_PAGES_AND_SECTIONS">
    <locale language="en">The script contains pages and sections at top-level.</locale>
    <cause>The script currently contains pages and sections at top-level.</cause>
    <action>All the pages should be under sections, or no section should be used.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_QUESTION_PAGE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID of the question page must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The ID has not been specified for the question page.</cause>
    <action>Specify the ID for the question page.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_RELATIONSHIP_PAGE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID of the relationship page must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The ID has not been specified for the relationship page.</cause>
    <action>Specify the ID for the relationship page.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SUMMARY_PAGE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID of the summary page must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The ID has not been specified for the summary page.</cause>
    <action>Specify the ID for the summary page.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ELEMENT_TITLE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A '%1s' title must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The title has not been specified for this element.</cause>
    <action>Specify a title for this element.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_ELEMENT_TITLE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID of the '%1s' title must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>An ID has not been specified for the title of this element.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for the title of this element.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_TEXT_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID of the '%1s' text must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>An ID has not been specified for the this text object.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for this text object.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ARGUMENT_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID must be specified for an argument.</locale>
    <cause>An ID has not been specified for this argument.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for this argument.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_COLUMN_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID must be specified for a column.</locale>
    <cause>An ID has not been specified for this column.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for this column.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SET_ATTRIBUTE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID must be specified for a set attribute.</locale>
    <cause>An ID has not been specified for this set attribute.</cause>
    <action>Specify an ID for this set attribute.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SET_ATTRIBUTE_EXPRESSION_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The expression must be specified for a set attribute.</locale>
    <cause>An expression has not been specified for this set attribute.</cause>
    <action>Specify an expression for this set attribute.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_VALIDATION_EXPRESSION_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The expression must be specified for a validation.</locale>
    <cause>An expression has not been specified for this validation.</cause>
    <action>Specify an expression for this validation.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_VALIDATION_MESSAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The message must be specified for a validation.</locale>
    <cause>A message has not been specified for this validation.</cause>
    <action>Specify a message for this validation.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_LAYOUT_TYPE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An invalid layout type has been specified for this '%1s'. It must be either "flow" or "compact-flow".</locale>
    <cause>An invalid layout type has been specified for this item.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid layout type for this item.</action>
  </message>    
  <message name="ID_INVALID_LAYOUT_LABEL_ALIGNMENT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An invalid label alignment has been specified for the layout of this '%1s'. It must be either "left", "right" or "center".</locale>
    <cause>An invalid label alignment has been specified for the layout of this item.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid label alignment for the layout of this item.</action>
  </message>    
  <message name="ID_CONDITION_EXPRESSION_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The condition expression has not been specified.</locale>
    <cause>An expression has not been specified for this condition.</cause>
    <action>Specify an expression for this condition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_EDIT_LINK_START_PAGE_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The start page attribute for the edit link has not been specified.</locale>
    <cause>The start page attribute has not been specified for this edit link.</cause>
    <action>Specify a start page attribute for this edit link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_EDIT_LINK_START_PAGE_NOT_IN_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">The start page identifier specified for the edit link does not refer to a page in the script.</locale>
    <cause>The start page identifier specified for the edit link does not refer to a page in the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid page identifier for the start page attribute of this edit link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_EDIT_LINK_END_PAGE_NOT_IN_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">The end page identifier specified for the edit link does not refer to a page in the script.</locale>
    <cause>The end page identifier specified for the edit link does not refer to a page in the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid page identifier for the end page attribute of this edit link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ADD_LINK_START_PAGE_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The start page attribute for the add link has not been specified.</locale>
    <cause>The start page attribute has not been specified for this add link.</cause>
    <action>Specify a start page attribute for this add link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ADD_LINK_START_PAGE_NOT_IN_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">The start page identifier specified for the add link does not refer to a page in the script.</locale>
    <cause>The start page identifier specified for the add link does not refer to a page in the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid page identifier for the start page attribute of this add link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ADD_LINK_END_PAGE_NOT_IN_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">The end page identifier specified for the add link does not refer to a page in the script.</locale>
    <cause>The end page identifier specified for the add link does not refer to a page in the script.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid page identifier for the end page attribute of this add link.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ELEMENT_NOT_SUPPORTED_BY_PARENT_ELEMENT">
    <locale language="en">This element can not be contained within a '%1s' element.</locale>
    <cause>An incompatible element has been added to a parent element.</cause>
    <action>Remove the incompatible element from the parent element.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_EMPTY_CLUSTER_ROW">
    <locale language="en">Rows must contain at least one visible element.</locale>
    <cause>The row contains nothing but skip fields.</cause>
    <action>Add any visible element to the row.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_QUESTION_ATTRIBUTE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The question attribute has not been specified for the question.</locale>
    <cause>The attribute has not been specified for the question.</cause>
    <action>Specify the attribute for the question.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LIST_QUESTION_LABEL_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The label of the list question must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The label has not been specified for the list question.</cause>
    <action>Specify the label for the list question.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LIST_QUESTION_ITEM_LABEL_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An item label must be specified for a list question.</locale>
    <cause>An item label has not been specified for the list question.</cause>
    <action>Specify an item label for the list question.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LIST_QUESTION_LABEL_FOR_ITEM_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A label must be specified for a list question item.</locale>
    <cause>A label has not been specified for the list question item.</cause>
    <action>Specify a label for the list question item.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LIST_QUESTION_ITEM_ATTRIBUTE_ID_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An attribute id for a list question item must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>An attribute id has not been specified for the list question item.</cause>
    <action>Specify an attribute id for the list question item.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LOOP_TYPE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The loop type must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The loop type not been specified for the loop.</cause>
    <action>Specify a loop type for the loop.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_LOOP_TYPE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The specified loop type is invalid. It must be either "for", "for-each" or "while".</locale>
    <cause>The specified loop type is invalid.</cause>
    <action>Specify a valid loop type for the loop.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_PROGRESS_VALUE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The progress value is invalid. It must be a value between 0 and 100 inclusive.</locale>
    <cause>A value has been specified for the progress attribute which is outside the range of 0 and 100 inclusive.</cause>
    <action>Specify a value for the progress attribute which is within the range of 0 to 100 inclusive.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ROWHELP_ATTRIBUTE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The ID attribute has not been specified for the row-help element.</locale>
    <cause>The ID attribute has not been specified for the row-help element.</cause>
    <action>Specify the ID attribute for the row-help element.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ROWHELP_TEXTS_CANNOT_HAVE_ALIASES">
    <locale language="en">An alias has been specified for a row help text on a list.</locale>
    <cause>An alias has been specified for a row help text on a list.</cause>
    <action>Remove the alias text for row help texts on lists.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_ROW_NOT_CORRECT_NUMBER_OF_ELEMENTS">
    <locale language="en">The footer row does not contain the correct number of elements, %1s expected but found %2s.</locale>
    <cause>The number of elements in the footer row is not equal to the total number of columns in the list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the number of elements in the footer row is equal to the total number of columns in the list.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_ROW_CAN_NOT_BE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">The footer row cannot be empty.</locale>
    <cause>The footer row does not contain any elements.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the number of elements in the footer row is not equal to the total number of columns in the list.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_ROW_HAS_ONLY_SKIP_FIELDS">
    <locale language="en">The footer row only contains skip fields.</locale>
    <cause>The footer row does not contain any visible elements.</cause>
    <action>Ensure there is at least one visible element in the footer row.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_MULTIPLE_FOOTER_ROWS_NOT_SUPPORTED">
    <locale language="en">The list contains more than one footer row.</locale>
    <cause>The list contains more than one footer row.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the list contains no more than one footer row.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_FIELD_TYPE_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">A type has not been specified for the footer field.</locale>
    <cause>A footer field without a type has been added to the list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the footer field has a type specified.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_FIELD_EXPRESSION_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">An expression has not been specified for the footer field.</locale>
    <cause>A footer field without an expression has been added to the list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the footer field has an expression specified.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_FOOTER_FIELD_ID_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">An ID has not been specified for the footer field.</locale>
    <cause>A footer field without an ID has been added to the list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the footer field has an ID specified.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DUPLICATE_LIST_LINK">
    <locale language="en">Duplicate action links were specified for a list.</locale>
    <cause>Duplicate action links were specified for a list.</cause>
    <action>Remove one of the duplicate links.</action>
  </message>
   <message name="ID_LINK_NOT_ALLOWED_IN_NON_SUMMARY_LIST">
    <locale language="en">An action link other than Delete was specified on a non-summary list.</locale>
    <cause>Only Delete links are supported on non-summary lists.</cause>
    <action>Remove the offending link.</action>
  </message>
   <message name="ID_LINK_NOT_ALLOWED_IN_RELATIONSHIP_SUMMARY_LIST">
    <locale language="en">An action link other than Edit was specified on a relationship summary list.</locale>
    <cause>Only Edit links are supported on relationship summary lists.</cause>
    <action>Remove the offending link.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_INVALID_CLUSTER_ID">
    <locale language="en">The cluster ID '%1s' is not valid as it contains a comma.</locale>
    <cause>Cluster IDs can't contain commas.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the cluster ID doesn't contain any comma.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DUPLICATE_CLUSTER_ID">
    <locale language="en">The cluster ID '%1s' has been defined multiple times on the page '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>Cluster IDs have to be unique within a page.</cause>
    <action>Ensure cluster IDs defined on a page are all different.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LIST_QUESTION_MAPPED_SAME_ATTRIBUTE_ERROR">
    <locale language="en">The list question '%1s' on the page '%2s' must have unique criteria.</locale>
    <cause>Multiple list questions mapped to the same entity and attribute must have unique criteria.</cause>
    <action>Ensure list questions mapped to the same entity and attrbute have unique criteria.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_ID_IN_SHOW_PAGE_ELEMENTS">
    <locale language="en">The element ID '%1s' referenced from an edit-link does not exist on the page '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>Script element IDs referenced on edit links have to exist on the page defined in 'start-page'.</cause>
    <action>Ensure element IDs referenced on an edit link exist on the page defined as the start page.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SHOW_PAGE_ELEMENTS_NOT_SUPPORTED_ON_RELATIONSHIP">
    <locale language="en">The element ID '%1s' cannot be referenced from an edit-link on a 'relationship-summary-list' element.</locale>
    <cause>'show-page-elements' attributes can only be defined on edit-links within 'cluster' or 'list' elements, but not within 'relationship-summary-list' elements.</cause>
    <action>Remove 'show-page-elements' attributes from edit-links within 'relationship-summary-list' elements.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_RELATIONSHIP_PAGE_NOT_CORRECT_NUMBER_OF_QUESTIONS">
    <locale language="en">The relationship page contains more than one question.</locale>
    <cause>The relationship page has more than one question defined.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the relationship page has at most one question defined.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_RELATIONSHIP_PAGE_NOT_CORRECT_NUMBER_OF_DISPLAYTEXTS">
    <locale language="en">The relationship page contains more than one display text.</locale>
    <cause>The relationship page has more than one display text defined.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the relationship page has at most one display text defined.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_RESET_READONLY_VALUE">
    <locale language="en">The 'clear-read-only-value' question attribute can only be specified in conjunction with the 'read-only-expression' attribute.</locale>
    <cause>The 'clear-read-only-value' question attribute can only be specified in conjunction with the 'read-only-expression' attribute.</cause>
    <action>Remove the offending attribute.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CUSTOM_OUTPUT_CLASS_NAME_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A class name must be specified for a 'custom-output' element.</locale>
    <cause>A class name was not entered into the 'class-name' attribute of the 'custom-output' element.</cause>
    <action>Specify a class name within the 'class-name' attribute for the 'custom-output' element.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CUSTOM_OUTPUT_DATA_ACCESSOR_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A data accessor must be specified for a 'custom-output' element.</locale>
    <cause>A class name was not entered into the 'data-accessor' attribute of the 'custom-output' element.</cause>
    <action>Specify a class name within the 'data-accessor' attribute for the 'custom-output' element.</action>
  </message>    
  <message name="ID_INFORMATIONAL_MESSAGE_IMAGE_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An image path must be specified for an 'informational-message' element.</locale>
    <cause>An image path was not entered into the 'image' attribute of the 'informational-message' element.</cause>
    <action>Specify an image path within the 'image' attribute for the 'informational-message' element.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_INFORMATIONAL_MESSAGE_EXPRESSION_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">An expression must be specified for an 'informational-message' element.</locale>
    <cause>An expression was not entered into the 'expression' attribute of the 'informational-message' element.</cause>
    <action>Specify an expression within the 'expression' attribute for the 'informational-message' element.</action>
  </message> 

  <!-- Subscript Validation Messages -->
  
  <message name="ID_INVALID_REFERENCE_TO_PARENT_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">An invalid reference to the parent script '%1s' has been specified in the script '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>An invalid reference to the parent script has been specified</cause>
    <action>Remove the reference.</action>
  </message>      

  <message name="ID_DUPLICATE_REFERENCES_TO_THE_SUBSCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">Duplicate references to the script '%1s' has been found in the scripts '%2s' and '%3s'.</locale>
    <cause>Duplicate calls to the same script from other scripts</cause>
    <action>Remove the duplicate references.</action>
  </message>      
 
  <message name="ID_DUPLICATE_REFERENCES">
    <locale language="en">Duplicate references to the script '%1s' has been found in the script '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>Duplicate calls to the same script in the script</cause>
    <action>Remove the duplicate references.</action>
  </message>      
  
  <message name="ID_SUBSCRIPT_DOES_NOT_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">The subscript %1s' with version '%2s' and type '%3s' does not exist.</locale>
    <cause>The subscript does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Create the subscript</action>
  </message>      
  
  
  <!-- not sure about these!!! -->
  <message name="ID_TEXT_VALUE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The '%1s' text must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A value has not been specified for the this text object.</cause>
    <action>Specify a value for this text object.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_ALIAS_TYPE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The type must be specified for an alias.</locale>
    <cause>A type has not been specified for this alias.</cause>
    <action>Specify a type for this alias.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_ICON_CURRENT_IMAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The current image of an icon must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The current image has not been specified for this icon.</cause>
    <action>Specify current image for this icon.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ICON_DISABLED_IMAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The disabled image of an icon must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The disabled image has not been specified for this icon.</cause>
    <action>Specify disabled image for this icon.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ICON_ENABLED_IMAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The enabled image of an icon must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The enabled image has not been specified for this icon.</cause>
    <action>Specify enabled image for this icon.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ICON_HOVER_IMAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The hover image of an icon must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The hover image has not been specified for this icon.</cause>
    <action>Specify hover image for this icon.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ICON_IMAGE_MUST_BE_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">The image of an icon must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>The image has not been specified for this icon.</cause>
    <action>Specify image for this icon.</action>
  </message>
        
</messages>