<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012,2020. All Rights Reserved.
 
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->  
<messages package="curam.intelligentevidencegathering.message">
  <message name="ID_FILE_NAME_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The file name supplied is invalid.</locale>
    <cause>The value for the file name entered was null or empty.</cause>
    <action>You must enter a valid file name that exists and is exact.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_EXECUTION_OBJECT_DELETE_ERROR">
    <locale language="en">Unable to delete the IEG script execution object.</locale>
    <cause>Unable to delete the recorded IEG script execution object as it does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Make sure the object was not previously deleted </action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_IMPORT_FAILED_CYCLE">
    <locale language="en">The import failed because the following scripts form a cycle: %1s.</locale>
    <cause>A script is defined as a subscript of an ancestor.</cause>
    <action>Check the scripts that are being imported</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_IMPORT_FAILED_UNDEFINED">
    <locale language="en">The import failed because the script '%1s' has a subscript '%2s' which doesn't exist.</locale>
    <cause>A script has a dependency on an unexisting subscript.</cause>
    <action>Check the scripts that are being imported</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_IMPORT_FAILED_SCRIPT_WITH_SAME_NAME_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">The import failed because the a script with the name '%1s' already exists. The specified script name must be unique.</locale>
    <cause>A script with the same name already exists on the database.</cause>
    <action>Specify a different script name when importing.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_IMPORT_FAILED_PARSER">
    <locale language="en">The import failed because of parsing problems.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DIRECTORY_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The IEG directory '%1s' does not exist.</locale>
    <cause>The directory that you specified does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the name and path of the directory is exact.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DIRECTORY_NAME_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The directory name supplied is invalid.</locale>
    <cause>The value for the directory entered was null or empty.</cause>
    <action>You must enter a valid directory name and path that exists and is exact.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_MODIFICATION_ERROR">
    <locale language="en">You cannot delete this Script. It is referenced by '%1s'.</locale>
    <cause>Script is referenced by at least one script.</cause>
    <action>Remove the referencing scripts.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A script with the ID '%1s' already exists.</locale>
    <cause>The script already exists with that ID, that you are trying to import.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the ID of the script is correct, and that it doesn't already exist.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_UNKNOWN_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">Question script with ID '%1s' does not exist.</locale>
    <cause>script with given script ID does not exist</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the script ID Exists</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLUSTER_ELEMENT_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">The element '%1s' has not been defined for the cluster '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>The element has not been defined for this cluster.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the element belongs to the specified cluster.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLUSTER_ELEMENT_ALREADY_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">Element '%1s' has already been defined for cluster '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>The specified element has already been used for this cluster.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the cluster is referenced correctly.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLUSTER_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">Cluster '%1s' has not been defined for question page '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>The cluster specified could not be found.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the reference ID for the cluster is exact.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_RELATIONSHIP_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A relationship between the scripts '%1s' and '%2s' already exists.</locale>
    <cause>There was already a relationship existing between the specified scripts.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the scripts exist, and that they are not already related.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ROOT_ENTITY_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The root entity for this script could not be found.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DATA_STORE_NOT_OPENED">
    <locale language="en">The common data store could not be opened.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCHEMA_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The specified schema could not be found.</locale>
    <cause>The common data store could not find the schema specified.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the schema is correctly specified and matches the declaration in the IEG script.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ENTITY_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">An entity could not be found in the common data store.</locale>
    <cause>The common data store could not find the entity specified.</cause>
    <action>Informational Only</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ENTITY_TYPE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The entity '%1s' could not be found in the common data store.</locale>
    <cause>The common data store could not find the entity specified.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the entity name in the schema matches the entity in the IEG script.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ENTITY_TYPE_NOT_DEFINED">
    <locale language="en">The entity '%1s' is not defined in the schema.</locale>
    <cause>The entity that was specified is not defined in the schema..</cause>
    <action>Ensure the entity name matches an entity in the schema.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_PERSON_ENTITY_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">A Person entity could not be found in the common data store.</locale>
    <cause>The common data store could not find the entity specified.</cause>
    <action>Informational Only</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">An attribute '%1s' of entity '%2s' could not be found in the common data store.</locale>
    <cause>The common data store could not find the attribute specified.</cause>
    <action>Informational Only</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_FILE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script file '%1s' does not exist.</locale>
    <cause>The file that you specified does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the name of the file is exact.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_EXECUTION_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script execution '%1s' does not exist.</locale>
    <cause>The IEG script execution that you specified does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the ID of the script execution is correct.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_EXECUTION_NOT_READABLE">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script execution '%1s' can't be read from the database.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_EXECUTION_NOT_WRITABLE">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script execution '%1s' can't be written to the database.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_UNMARSHALL_ERROR">
    <locale language="en">Unable to unmarshal the data. The error message is '%1s'.</locale>
    <cause>A problem occurred while `unmarshalling` data</cause>
    <action>Informational only</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ANSWERS_NOT_FOR_CURRENT_PAGE">
    <locale language="en">The answers provided are not for the current page.</locale>
    <cause>The answers returned are not for the current page.</cause>
    <action>The answers you entered are not for the current question file, be sure to make it the exact question file.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ACTION_LINK_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The action link specified could not be found.</locale>
    <cause>The action link encountered by the IEG player could not be found or is the wrong type.</cause>
    <action>Informational only</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ACTION_LINK_PAGE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The question page specified by the action link, '%1s', was not encountered during script execution.</locale>
    <cause>The action link selected does not refer to a page that was encountered during script execution.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the action link refers to a page that was encountered during script execution.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_ACTION_LINK">
    <locale language="en">An invalid action link was encountered during script execution.</locale>
    <cause>An action link was not placed in either a cluster or a list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that all action links are only placed in either clusters or lists.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DOB_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">Age could not be determined because a value for 'Person.dateOfBirth' could not be found in the datastore.</locale>
    <cause>A 'dateOfBirth' attribute needs to be present on the Person entity in order to determine age.</cause>
    <action>Specify 'dateOfBirth' on the Person entity.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_ENTITY_ID">
    <locale language="en">The entity id '%1s' is invalid.</locale>
    <cause>The entity id is not in the correct form..</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the entity id is specified in the form 'EnityName.AttributeName'.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_EXPRESSION">
    <locale language="en">The expression '%1s' is invalid.</locale>
    <cause>The expression specified must be a Boolean expression.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that all attributes in the expression are mandatory or have a default value.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_EXPRESSION_WITH_CAUSE">
    <locale language="en">The expression '%1s' is invalid. %2s.</locale>
    <cause>%2</cause>
    <action>Ensure that all attributes in the expression are mandatory or have a default value. Each attribute must be specified on an entity in the associated datastore schema.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DIRECTORY_CREATION_FAILED">
    <locale language="en">The output directory %1s couldn't be created.</locale>
    <cause>An existing output directory has to be supplied, or the necessary rights to create it must exist.</cause>
    <action>Supply an existing output directory or check that creation rights exist.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="RUN_QUERYEXPRESSION">
    <locale language="en">Query expression must be Boolean: %1s</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="RUN_IOEXCEPTION">
    <locale language="en">IOException while loading store: %1s</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_ERR_INVOKING_CUSTOM_OUTPUT_DATA_ACCESSOR">
    <locale language="en">There was an error while trying to invoke the custom output data accessor %1s</locale>
    <cause>There was an error while trying to invoke the custom output data accessor.</cause>
    <action>Ensure the custom output data accessor has been configured correctly.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="RUN_PLAYERBEHAVIOUR_INSTANTIATION_EXCEPTION">
    <locale language="en">Could not instantiate the player behaviour class %1s.</locale>
	<cause>There was an error while trying to instantiate the player behaviour.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that the class exists, is correctly named and implements the correct interface.</action>
  </message>
  
  <!-- Generic validation messages -->
  <message name="INFO_ID_IEG_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_VALID">
    <locale language="en">The specified IEG script definition is valid.</locale>
    <cause>Text Only</cause>
    <action>For informational use only.</action>
  </message>
  
  <!-- Validation error messages associated with validating an IEG script against the associated datastore schema -->
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_CANNOT_BE_VALIDATED_AGAINST_SELECTED_SCHEMA">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script definition can not be validated against the selected schema.</locale>
    <cause>The IEG script definition can not be validated against the selected schema.</cause>
    <action>Select an appropriate datastore schema with which to validate the IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_ENTITY_NOT_PRESENT_IN_DATASTORE">
    <locale language="en">The entity named '%1s' specified in the IEG script definition is not present in the associated datastore schema.</locale>
    <cause>The entity specified in the script definition is not present in the associated datastore schema.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to specify the entity or the associated datastore schema must be updated to include the entity.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_PARENT_CHILD_ENTITY_RELATIONSHIP">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script definition entity relationship between the parent entity named '%1s' and the child entity named '%2s' is invalid. No such parent child entity relationship exists in the associated datastore schema.</locale>
    <cause>The specified parent child entity relationship in the IEG script definition is invalid as no such relationship exists in the associated datastore schema.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to specify the correct parent child entity relationship or the associated datastore schema must be updated to include the valid parent child relationship.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_MULTIPLE_RELATIONSHIP_PARENT"> 
    <locale language="en">The IEG script definition entity relationship between the parent entity named '%1s' and the child entity named '%2s' is invalid. A '%2s' entity cannot have multiple parents when a relationship-page is used.</locale> 
    <cause>The specified parent child entity relationship in the IEG script definition is invalid as it can only be used in one context when a relationship-page is used.</cause> 
    <action>The IEG script and  the associated datastore schema must be updated to define a different child entity name to be used in contexts other than relationship-page and relationship-summary-list.</action> 
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_ATTRIBUTE_DOES_NOT_EXIST_ON_ENTITY">
    <locale language="en">The attribute named '%1s' associated with the entity '%2s' in the IEG script definition is invalid. No such entity attribute relationship exists in the associated datastore schema.</locale>
    <cause>The attribute associated with the specified entity in the script definition is not present in the associated datastore schema.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to specify a valid attribute for the entity or the associated datastore schema must be updated to specify a valid attribute for that entity.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_DATASTORE_REQUIRED_RELATIONSHIP_ENTITY_NOT_PRESENT">
    <locale language="en">The entity named '%1s' must be present in the datastore schema to allow relationship data to be captured or displayed.</locale>
    <cause>The Person or Relationship entities are not present in the datastore but there is a relationship page present in the script.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to remove the relationship pages or the associated datastore schema must be updated to specify the required entities.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_DATASTORE_REQUIRED_RELATIONSHIP_ENTITY_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_PRESENT">
    <locale language="en">The attribute named '%1s' must be present on the entity named '%2s' when relationship data is being captured or displayed.</locale>
    <cause>The correct Relationship entity attribute is not present in the datastore but there is a relationship page present in the script containing a question.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to remove the relationship page question or the associated datastore schema must be updated to specify the required entity attribute.</action>
  </message>   
  <message name="ID_REQUIRED_RELATIONSHIP_ENTITY_ATTRIBUTE_FOR_QUESTION_NOT_PRESENT">
    <locale language="en">The attribute named '%1s' must be present on the entity named '%2s' when a question data is being captured or displayed on a relationship page.</locale>
    <cause>The correct Relationship entity attribute is not present in the datastore but there is a relationship page present in the script containing a question.</cause>
    <action>Either the IEG script must be updated to remove the relationship page question or the associated datastore schema must be updated to specify the required entity attribute.</action>
  </message>
  
  <!-- Validation error messages associated with validating an IEG script against the IEG script definition schema -->  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_INVALID_AGAINST_IEG_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_SCHEMA">
    <locale language="en">The IEG script definition is invalid against the schema. The schema error is "%1s"</locale>
    <cause>The IEG script definition is invalid against the schema.</cause>
    <action>The IEG script definition needs to be updated to make it valid against the IEG script definition schema.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_VISITED_PAGES_NOT_UPDATED_CORRECTLY">
    <locale language="en">The list of visited pages is inconsistent with the operation being performed.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <!-- Validation error messages associated with the IEG Editing and Runtime APIs -->
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_ELEMENT_VALIDATOR_NOT_SPECIFIED">
    <locale language="en">A validator has not been specified for the script element of type %1s.</locale>
    <cause>A validator has not been specified for this script element.</cause>
    <action>Informational Only</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_IDENTIFIER_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The script identifier must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A script identifier must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a identifier for the IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_VERSION_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The script version must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A script version must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a version for the IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_TYPE_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The script type must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A script type must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a type for the IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_NAME_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The script name must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A script name must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a name for the IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCHEMA_NAME_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The schema name must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A schema name must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a schema name.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_EXECUTION_IDENTIFIER_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The script execution identifier must be supplied.</locale>
    <cause>A script execution identifier must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a script execution identifier.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLONE_SCRIPT_IDENTIFIER_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The new script identifier to be used to clone the script definition must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A new script identifier must be specified for the clone script definition operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a new identifier for the cloned IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLONE_SCRIPT_VERSION_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The new script version to be used to clone the script definition must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A new script version must be specified for the clone script definition operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a new version for the cloned IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_CLONE_SCRIPT_TYPE_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The new script type to be used to clone the script definition must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A new script type must be specified for the clone script definition operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a new type for the cloned IEG script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_TO_BE_CLONED_DOES_NOT_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">The script definition with identifier '%1s', version '%2s' and type '%3s' does not exist and therefore cannot be cloned.</locale>
    <cause>The script definition specified to be cloned does not exist.</cause>
    <action>Choose another script definition to clone.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_DEFINITION_TO_CLONE_TO_ALREADY_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A script definition with identifier '%1s', version '%2s' and type '%3s' already exists and therefore this script identifier cannot be used for the cloned script definition identifier.</locale>
    <cause>The script definition to clone to already exists.</cause>
    <action>A different script definition identifier should be specified for the cloned script definition.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_QUESTION_PAGE_IDENTIFIER_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The question page identifier must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A question page identifier must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a identifier for the question page.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_QUESTION_IDENTIFIER_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The question identifier must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A question identifier must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a identifier for the question.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_LOCALE_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">The locale must be specified.</locale>
    <cause>A locale must be specified for the operation to succeed.</cause>
    <action>Supply a locale.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_QUESTION_CANNOT_BE_FOUND_ON_PAGE">
    <locale language="en">The question with identifier '%1s' cannot be found on the page with identifier '%2s'.</locale>
    <cause>The question cannot be found on the specified page.</cause>
    <action>Supply a valid page and question.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_NOTES_ATTRIBUTE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">A scriptNotes attribute must exist in the datastore</locale>
    <cause>A scriptNotes attribute must exist on the Application entity in the datastore schema in order to use script notes.</cause>
    <action>Add a script notes attribute to the Application entity in the datastore schema.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_QUESTION_TYPE_BOOLEAN_AND_MANDATORY">
    <locale language="en">The question with identifier '%1s' and internal identifier '%2s' has type Boolean and marked as mandatory.It will not be possible to select No as the answer for this question in the player as there will be only one check box selectable.</locale>
    <cause>The question has type Boolean and marked as mandatory.</cause>
    <action>Please mark the question as not mandatory.</action>
  </message>
  <!-- Validation warning messages associated with deprecated artifacts -->
  <message name="ID_DEPRECATION_CANNOT_VALIDATE_EXPRESSION">
    <locale language="en">Cannot validate expression '%1s'.</locale>
    <cause>An expression could not be validated</cause>
    <action>Check the expression is syntactically valid.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DEPRECATION_CANNOT_VALIDATE_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">Cannot validate script.</locale>
    <cause>A script could not be validated</cause>
    <action>Check the script file contains well-formed XML.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_SCRIPT_CURRENTLY_EXECUTING">
    <locale language="en">This script cannot be deleted because there is an instance currently in execution.</locale>
    <cause>An instance of this script is currently executing.</cause>
    <action>Complete all existing instances of this script.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_BOM_SUBSCRIPT_DOESNT_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">A relationship between the script '%1s' and its subscript '%1s' cannot be added as the subscript doesn't exist.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_BOM_DOES_NOT_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">The script does not exist.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="BOM_INFORMATIONAL_NAME">
    <locale language="en">IEG Script</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="RUN_EXPRESSION_INTEGER">
    <locale language="en">Expression must be an integer: %1s</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="RUN_PAGE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The page represented by '%1s' could not be found in the definition for '%2s'</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SUBSCRIPT_FILE_READ_ONLY">
    <locale language="en">The subscript file %1s is read only and cannot be overwritten.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DEPRECATION_COMMENT">
    <locale language="en">[deprecation comment] %1s</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="PARSER_ERROR_HANDLER">
    <locale language="en">%1s at line %2d in the IEG script definition XML file.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_VALID">
    <locale language="en">The script %1s is valid</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_HEADER">
    <locale language="en">The validation results for the  IEG script file:  %1s</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_SCRIPT">
    <locale language="en">IEG Script (%1s) Validation Result Begin</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_WARNINGS">
    <locale language="en">Warnings</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_WARNING_PREFIX_DEPRECATION">
    <locale language="en">%1s warning: [deprecation] </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_WARNING_PREFIX">
    <locale language="en">%1s warning: </locale>
  </message>
  <message name="CMD_LINE_VALIDATOR_END">
    <locale language="en">IEG Script Validation Result End</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_VALIDATOR_SECTION">
    <locale language="en">Section</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_VALIDATOR_PAGE">
    <locale language="en">Page</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_SCRIPT_VALIDATOR_SCRIPT_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">script attribute</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_HELP_ON_INNER_LIST">
    <locale language="en">Row help was specified on the inner list '%1s' of a nested list.</locale>
    <cause>It is not valid to specify row help on the inner list of a nested list.</cause>
    <action>Ensure that row help is only specified for the outer list of a nested list.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_INVALID_DATATYPE">
    <locale language="en">Invalid data type '%1s'.</locale>
    <cause>The data type could not be recognized.</cause>
    <action>Be sure that the data type you entered is in line with the data types used within the framework.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="ID_DOMAIN_INITIALIZATION_FAILED">
    <locale language="en">Domain definition initialization failed.</locale>
    <cause>Domain Initialization failed due to the following domainException being thrown: '%1s'</cause>
    <action>Use the additional Information supplied by the error to help fix it.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="DUPLICATE_DOMAINS_FOUND_EXCEPTION">
    <locale language="en">One or more new duplicate domains were found.</locale>
    <cause>When running the tool to detect whether duplicate domains exist between the Curam model and Curam datastore, one or more new duplicate domains were found.</cause>
    <action>Ensure any domains that have been configured are uniquely named.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="DUPLICATE_DOMAINS_FOUND_ERROR">
    <locale language="en">ERROR: Duplicate domain found</locale>
    <cause>When running the tool to detect whether duplicate domains exist between the Curam model and Curam datastore, one or more new duplicate domains were found.</cause>
    <action>Ensure any domains that have been configured are uniquely named.</action>
  </message>
  <message name="DUPLICATE_DOMAINS_FOUND_WARNING">
    <locale language="en">WARNING: Known duplicate domain detected</locale>
    <cause>When running the tool to detect whether duplicate domains exist between the Curam model and Curam datastore, one or more pre-existing duplicate domains were found.</cause>
    <action>This message is for informational purposes only.</action>
  </message>  
  <message name="ERR_INVALID_QUESTION_ID">
    <locale language="en">The question id '%1s' is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
</messages>