<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<messages package="curam.ca.gc.bdmoas.message">
  <message name="ERR_CONSENT_EVIDENCE_MISSING">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because Consent and Declaration is missing or incomplete.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_EVIDENCE_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because evidence issues exists on Application case.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_VERIFICATION_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because verifications exists on application case.</locale>
  </message>
  
   <message name="ERR_GISTASK_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because tasks are still open on application case.</locale>
  </message> 
  
  <message name="ERR_TASK_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because tasks are still open on application case for either missing residence period, Nature of Absence, Direct deposit link, Verification of authorized person or client has an existing withdrawal request has not been created.</locale>
  </message>   
  
  <message name="ERR_PROSPECT_PERSON_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because applicant is a prospect person.</locale>
  </message>   
  
  <message name="TRASANCTION_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">An in-progress %1s request for %2s for %3s exists.</locale>
  </message>  
  
  <message name="ERR_GIS_PROSPECT_PERSON_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because prospect person exists on Application case.</locale>
  </message> 
  
    
  <message name="ERR_GIS_OAS_ISSUE">
    <locale language="en">GIS Benefit cannot be authorized due to OAS Pension benefit being in pending status.</locale>
  </message> 
  <message name="ERR_DUPLICATE_APPLICATION">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized because this is a duplicate application.</locale>
  </message>  
   
  <message name="ERR_OPEN_TASK">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be authorized as open tasks exist.</locale>
  </message> 
  <message name="ERR_CLOSE_ALL_BENEFITS_NOT_PENDING">
    <locale language="en">Benefits cannot be closed because one or more benefit is NOT in pending status.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_CLOSE_ALL_BENEFITS_OPEN_TASK">
    <locale language="en">Benefits cannot be closed as open tasks exist.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_CLOSE_BENEFIT_MANDATORY_TASKS_OPEN">
    <locale language="en">The benefit cannot be closed because mandatory tasks are still open on application case for either missing residence period, Nature of Absence or Direct deposit link has not been created.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_REOPEN_DATE_MUST_NOT_BE_BEFORE_APPLICATION_SUBMISSION_DATE">
    <locale language="en">The Reopen date should not be before the application submission date.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_REOPEN_DATE_AFTER_CURRENT_DATE">
    <locale language="en">The date should not be greater than the current date.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_GIS_REOPEN_WHEN_OAS_BENEFIT_CLOSED">
    <locale language="en">GIS Benefit cannot be reopened because OAS Benefit is either Closed or Withdrawn.</locale>
  </message>
  
    <message name="ERR_REOPEN_WHEN_BENEFIT_ALREADY_APPROVED">
    <locale language="en">Benefit has already been approved for the applicant.</locale>
  </message>
  
</messages>
