<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.
 
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->  

<!-- 
Copyright 2008 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.
This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.workspaceservices.message">
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_FAILURE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER008: CDME Mapping Error. Failed attempting to map Data Store Entity of type %1s to Entity type %2s. Entity XML is %3s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_EVIDENCE_CREATION_FAILURE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER009: CDME Mapping Error. Failed attempting to create evidence Entity of type %1s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_PDF_FORM_FAILURE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER010: CDME Mapping Error. Failed attempting to complete PDF forms. More than one form is registered against program type %1s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_SETTING_ALTERNATE_ID_TYPE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER011: CDME Mapping Error. Error setting the alternate id type for a Prospect Person: %1s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_SETTING_ALTERNATE_ID_TYPE_INVALID_VALUE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER012: CDME Mapping Error. Error setting the alternate ID type for a Prospect Person or Person: %1s set to invalid value %2s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_ILLEGAL_STATE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER013: CDME Mapping Error. Error the Evidence Application Builder has not been correctly configured. Mapping cannot proceed.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_NO_CONFIGURATION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER014: CDME Mapping Error. Failed attempting to map evidence of type %1s. Check that this evidence type is listed in the Mapping Configuration.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_NO_PARENT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">APROCER015: CDME Mapping Error. Attempting to map a child evidence entity of type %1s but failed to find mapped parent with id %2d.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_UNMARSHALING_APPLICATION_XML">
    <locale language="en">APROCER016: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when trying to unmarshal the application XML.</locale>
  </message>  
  <message name="ERR_SETTING_XML_FIELD_VALUE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER017: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when trying to set the field '%1s' with the value '%2s'.</locale>
  </message>  	
  <message name="ERR_XML_CREATION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER018: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when trying to create the PDF document. Please contact your administrator.</locale>
  </message>  		
  <message name="ERR_FORM_VALUE_TO_CODETABLE_DESCRIPTION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER019: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when trying to create the PDF document. The form code %1s could not be mapped to a codetable description. Please contact your administrator.</locale>
  </message>  			
  <message name="ERR_CREATING_EXTENSION_HANDLER">
    <locale language="en">APROCER020: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when trying a WorkspaceServices mapping extension handler. The class %1s could not be initialized. Please contact your administrator.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_MISSING_SOURCE_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">APROCER021: CDME Mapping Error. An error occurred when mapping %1s to %2s. Missing source attribute %3s from Datastore.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_BADLY_FORMED_IDENTIFIER_IN_EXPRESSION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER022: CDME Mapping Error. The attribute %1s in an expression is badly formed. Attributes used in this context must be of the form EntityName.attributeName.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_BAD_CONFIGURATION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER023: CDME Mapping Error. The wrong ApplicationBuilderConfiguration class %1s is being used with ApplicationBuilder type %2s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_FV_DATASTORE_MAPPING_CONFIG_MANDATORY_NAME">
    <locale language="en">APROCER024: CDME Mapping Error. Failed creating DataStoreMappingConfig, no name specified.</locale>
  </message>   				
  <message name="ERR_XRV_DATASTORE_MAPPING_CONFIG_NON_UNIQUE_NAME">
    <locale language="en">APROCER025: CDME Mapping Error. Failed creating DataStoreMappingConfig, the name %1s is not unique.</locale>
  </message>  
  <message name="ERR_DATASTORE_MAPPING_NO_SUCH_SCHEMA">
    <locale language="en">APROCER026: CDME Mapping Error. The Mapping to Datastore had to be abandoned because the schema %1s is not registered.</locale>
  </message> 	
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_PARSING_MAPPING_SPECIFICATION">
    <locale language="en">APROCER027: CDME Mapping Error. There was a problem parsing the Mapping Specification.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- http://cems.curamsoftware.com:8080/browse/GUM-2109 -->
  <message name="ERR_FV_EFFECTIVE_DATE_IN_PAST">
    <locale language="en">The Effective Date must be on or after today.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_XRV_RECORD_WITH_SAME_EFF_DATE_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">An In Edit record already exists with an Effective Date of %1d.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_XRV_RELEASED_RECORD_WITH_SAME_EFFECTIVE_DATE_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A Released mapping already exists with an effective date of %1d. If you proceed, this existing mapping will be superseded by your new mapping. Are you sure you want to release this mapping?</locale>
  </message>  
  <message name="INF_XRV_RELEASED_RECORD_WITH_EARLIER_EFFECTIVE_DATE_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">Released mappings already exist with effective dates before that of your new mapping. If you proceed, your new mapping will supersede the existing mappings from %1d. Are you sure you want to release this mapping?</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_XRV_RELEASED_RECORD_WITH_LATER_EFFECTIVE_DATE_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">Released mappings already exist with effective dates that are after your new mapping. If you proceed, your new mapping will only be active until the nearest effective date. Are you sure you want to release this mapping?</locale>
  </message>    
  <!-- BEGIN, GUM-3942, CH -->
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_PERSON">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error ApplicationID=%2n. Error creating person with datastore ID: %3n.</locale>
  </message>    
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_PROSPECT_PERSON">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error ApplicationID=%2n. Error creating prospect person with datastore ID: %3n.</locale>
  </message>      
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_RELATIONSHIPS">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error. Error creating relationship of type %2s between person with datastore ID: %3n and person with datastore ID: %4n.</locale>
  </message>      
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_CASE">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error ApplicationID=%2n. Error creating case associated with program reference: %3s</locale>
  </message>        
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_HANDLER_PERFORM_MAPPING">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error. Error mapping datastore entity %2s, attribute %3s to evidence entity %4s, attribute %5s.</locale>
  </message>        
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_HANDLER_PERFORM_MAPPING_SET_ATTRIBUTE">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error. Error with "set attribute" mapping on evidence entity %2s, attribute %3s.</locale>
  </message>          
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_HANDLER_PERFORM_MAPPING_MAP_ADDRESS">
    <locale language="en">%1s: CDME Mapping Error. Error with "map address" mapping on datastore entity %2s, to evidence entity %3s, attribute %4s.</locale>
  </message>          
  <!-- END, GUM-3942 -->
  <message name="ERR_MAPPING_RECORD_CHECKED_EXCEPTION_THROWN">
    <locale language="en">APROCER043: Record checked exception that occurred during evidence mapping.</locale>
  </message> 
</messages>

