<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
  
  PID 5725-H26
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2003, 2014. All rights reserved.
  
  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp. 
-->
<!-- 
Copyright 2003-2005 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FILENOTFOUND">
    <locale language="en">Load Payment Received could not be performed as the file "%1s" does not exist.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_AMOUNT_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Amount for payment received instrument is not populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_AMOUNT_INVAILD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Amount for payment received instrument is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_CURRENCYTYPE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Currency for payment received instrument is not populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_DEPOSITSLIPNUMBER_INVAILD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Deposit Slip Number for payment received instrument is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_EFFECTIVEDATE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Effective Date for payment received instrument is not populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_EFFECTIVEDATE_INVAILD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Effective Date for payment received instrument is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_RECEIPTMETHODTYPE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Receipt Method Type for payment received instrument is not populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_RECEIPTNUMBER_INVAILD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Receipt Number for payment received instrument is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_RECEIVEDDATE_INVAILD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the Received Date for payment received instrument is invalid.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_CHEQUENO_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Check do not have check number details populated.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Cheque do not have cheque number details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_DESTBANKACCOUNTNAME_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have destination bank account name details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_DESTBANKACCOUNTNUMBER_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have destination bank account number details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_DESTBANKSORTCODE_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have destination bank account sort code details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- BEGIN, CR00407584, SS -->
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_DESTIBAN_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have destination IBAN details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_DESTBIC_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have destination bank account BIC details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- END, CR00407584 -->
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_LEDGERNO_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Cash do not have ledger number details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_ORIGINBANKACCOUNTNAME_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have originating bank account name details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_ORIGINBANKACCOUNTNUMBER_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have originating bank account number details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_ORIGINBANKSORTCODE_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have originating bank account sort code details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- BEGIN, CR00407584, SS -->
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_ORIGINIBAN_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have originating bank account IBAN details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_ORIGINBIC_RECEIPTMETHOD">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as payment received instruments of type Giro do not have originating bank account BIC details populated.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- END, CR00407584 -->
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_TOTALAMOUNT_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalAmount control total does not equal the total Amount received.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_TOTALCHQAMT_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalCheckAmount control total does not equal the total check amount received.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalCheckAmount control total does not equal the total cheque amount received.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_TOTALCSHAMT_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalCashAmount control total does not equal the total cash amount received.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_TOTALRECORDS_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalRecords control total does not equal the total number of records in the file.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_TOTALSOAMT_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">The payment received file cannot be loaded as the TotalStandingOrderAmount control total does not equal the total standing order amount received.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_LOADPAYMENTRECEIVED_SUB">
    <locale language="en">Report from LoadPaymentsReceived batch job run on %1s at %2s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_PMTRECEIVED_FV_LBYREFNUMBER_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">Invalid Liability Reference Number %1s.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_AMOUNT_PMTRECVD_RECS">
    <locale language="en">Total amount for all records loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_CASH_AMOUNT_PMTRECVD_RECS">
    <locale language="en">Total amount for all Cash payments loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_CHQ_AMOUNT_PMTRECVD_RECS">
    <locale language="en">Total amount for all Check payments loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Total amount for all Cheque payments loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_PMTRECVD_RECS">
    <locale language="en">Total number of records loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_SO_AMOUNT_PMTRECVD_RECS">
    <locale language="en">Total amount for all Standing Order payments loaded from the payment received file: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_TOTAL_SUSPENSEITEMS_CREATED">
    <locale language="en">Total number of Suspense Account record(s) created: %1n</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="INF_LOAD_PMTS_RECEIVED">
    <locale language="en">LoadPmtsRecvd</locale>
  </message>
</messages>