<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.

  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!-- 
Copyright 2003-2005 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_COMM_DATE_IN_FUTURE">
    <locale language="en">The date for this communication must not be in the future.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_DATE_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must supply a from date for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_EMAIL_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">%1s has no email address and cannot receive email communications. You must supply an email address.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_NAME_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must supply a correspondent name for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_PHONE_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must provide the phone number for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_PROFORMA_TYPE_BLANK">
    <locale language="en">You must select a pro forma type for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_SUBJECT_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must supply a subject for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_TEXT_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must supply freeform text for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_FAX_NOT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must provide the fax number for this communication.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_NO_SENDER_EMAIL">
    <locale language="en">To send an email the senders email address must be specified. At the moment neither the current User or the organization has a valid email address that can be used as the senders email. Please update one of these email addresses before trying to send this email. Note that in the case of the User it is the business email address that is used and not the personal email address.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >To send an email the senders email address must be specified. At the moment neither the current User or the organisation has a valid email address that can be used as the senders email. Please update one of these email addresses before trying to send this email. Note that in the case of the User it is the business email address that is used and not the personal email address.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_INCORRECT_CORRESPONDENT_SUPPLIED">
    <locale language="en">You must supply one correspondent.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_METHOD_PHONE_NEED_TYPECODE_BLANK">
    <locale language="en">No communication type exists for method type phone. Please reset the communication type to blank.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_COMM_TYPE_CODE_BLANK">
    <locale language="en">You must select a communication type for this method of communication</locale>
  </message>
</messages>