<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  IBM Confidential
  
  OCO Source Materials
  
  PID 5725-H26
  
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2003,2013
  
  The source code for this program is not published or otherwise divested
  of its trade secrets, irrespective of what has been deposited with the US Copyright Office
-->
<!-- 
Copyright 2003-2005, 2007 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_XRV_LEADPOSITION_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">A lead position must exist for the parent organization unit before a child organization unit can be added to it.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A lead position must exist for the parent organisation unit before a child organisation unit can be added to it.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_XRV_PARENTCHILD">
    <locale language="en">This organization unit cannot be added because the parent organization unit is not in the same organization structure.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This organisation unit cannot be added because the parent organisation unit is not in the same organisation structure.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_NAME_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Organization unit name must be entered.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Organisation unit name must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_XRV_NAME_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">An Organization Unit with this name already exists in this structure.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Organisation unit name already exists in this organisation structure.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_STATUS_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Organization unit status must be entered.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Organisation unit status must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_STRUCTURE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Organization structure must be entered.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Organisation structure must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_CREATION_DATE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Creation date must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_XRV_ROOTORGUNIT_EXISTS">
    <locale language="en">A root organization unit already exists for this organization structure.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A root organisation unit already exists for this organisation structure.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_PARENT_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">A parent organization unit must be entered.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A parent organisation unit must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_CHILD_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">A child organization unit must be entered.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A child organisation unit must be entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_FV_PARENT_ALREADYPARENT">
    <locale language="en">The parent organization unit selected is already the parent organization for this organization structure.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >The parent organisation unit selected is already the parent organisation for this organisation structure.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PARENTUNIT_XRV_IN_OTHER_STRUCTURE">
    <locale language="en">The parent organization unit must be in the same organization structure as this organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >The parent organisation unit must be in the same organisation structure as this organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_CHILD_ORGUNITS_STILL_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">Cannot delete this organization unit as there are still active child organization units.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Cannot delete this organisation unit as there are still active child organisation units.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_ASSIGNEDPOSITIONS_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">Cannot delete this organization unit as there are still users assigned to positions within the organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Cannot delete this organisation unit as there are still users assigned to positions within the organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ADD_CHILD_ORGUNITS_CANCELED_PARENT_ORGUNIT">
    <locale language="en">Cannot add a child organization unit to a canceled parent organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Cannot add a child organisation unit to a cancelled parent organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGUNIT_NO_LEAD_POSIITON_EXIST">
    <locale language="en">There must be at least one lead position for the parent organization unit which you are adding the child organization unit to.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >There must be at least one lead position for the parent organisation unit which you are adding the child organisation unit to.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ADD_CHILD_ORGUNITS_CANCELED_ORGANISATION_STRUCTURE">
    <locale language="en">Cannot add or modify an organization unit to a canceled organization structure.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Cannot add or modify an organisation unit to a cancelled organisation structure.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ORGANISATIONSECURITY_CHECK_FAILED">
    <locale language="en">You do not have the required privileges to perform this task.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_WORK_ORGUNIT_XRV_CASE_OWNER">
    <locale language="en">This organization unit is the owner of one or more cases and therefore cannot be canceled.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >This organisation unit is the owner of one or more cases and therefore cannot be cancelled.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_ORGUNIT_TEMPORAL_EVIDENCE_APPROVAL_CLOSED_ORGUNIT">
    <locale language="en">You cannot create organization unit temporal evidence approval on a cancelled organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >You cannot create organisation unit temporal evidence approval on a cancelled organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_RESOURCE_CLOSED_ORGUNIT">
    <locale language="en">You cannot create resource on a cancelled organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >You cannot create resource on a cancelled organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_CREATE_POSITION_TEMPORAL_EVIDENCE_APPROVAL_CLOSED_ORGUNIT">
    <locale language="en">You cannot create position temporal evidence approval on a cancelled organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >You cannot create position temporal evidence approval on a cancelled organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_ASSIGN_RESOURCE_CLOSED_ORGUNIT">
    <locale language="en">You cannot assign resource on a cancelled organization unit.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >You cannot assign resource on a cancelled organisation unit.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- BEGIN, CR00388421, AC-->
  <message name="INF_ORGUNIT_SEARCH_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">There are no matching items based on the Search Criteria entered.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- END, CR00388421-->
  <!-- BEGIN, CR00407060, RD -->
  <message name="ERR_ORGANISATIONSECURITY_MODIFY_USER_CHECK_FAILED">
    <locale language="en">You do not have sufficient privileges to maintain a user for %1s.</locale>
  </message>
  <!-- END, CR00407060 -->
</messages>
