<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2012. All Rights Reserved.

  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->
<!-- 
Copyright 2003-2005 Curam Software Ltd.
All rights reserved.

This software is the confidential and proprietary information of Curam
Software, Ltd. ("Confidential Information").  You shall not
disclose such Confidential Information and shall use it only in accordance
with the terms of the license agreement you entered into with Curam Software.
-->
<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUCTION_FV_METHOD_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">Only Cash and Check methods of receipt are supported for online receipt of payments.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Only Cash and Cheque methods of receipt are supported for online receipt of payments.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_LEDGERNO_AND_CHEQUENO_SET">
    <locale language="en">Both Check Number and Ledger Number were specified. Details for 2 different types of Instrument (Check and Cash) cannot apply to a single payment received.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >Both Cheque Number and Ledger Number were specified. Details for 2 different types of Instrument (Cheque and Cash) cannot apply to a single payment received.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_XFV_NUMBER_COMBO_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">An invalid combination exists for the payment received instrument details specified. Please check that a check instrument has a check number or a cash instrument has a ledger number.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >An invalid combination exists for the payment received instrument details specified. Please check that a cheque instrument has a cheque number or a cash instrument has a ledger number.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_AMOUNT_NOT_POSITIVE">
    <locale language="en">The payment received being captured must have a positive amount.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_AMOUNT_ZERO">
    <locale language="en">Cannot process a Payment Received with a zero amount.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_EFFECTIVEDATE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Cannot process a Payment Received with a blank Effective Date.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_LBYREFNUMBER_INVALID">
    <locale language="en">Invalid Liability Reference Number entered. Please modify or remove.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_RECEIVEDDATE_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">Cannot process a Payment Received with a blank Received Date.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_RECEIVEPAYMENT_FV_RECVDATE_IN_FUTURE">
    <locale language="en">Cannot process a Payment Received with a Received Date in the future.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_CASH_LEDGER_NUMBER_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">A ledger number must be supplied for cash payments.</locale>
  </message>
  <message name="ERR_PMTRECEIVEDINSTRUMENT_FV_CHECK_CHECKNUMBER_EMPTY">
    <locale language="en">A check number must be supplied for check payments.</locale>
    <locale
      country="GB"
      language="en"
    >A cheque number must be supplied for cheque payments.</locale>
  </message>
</messages>