<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Licensed Materials - Property of IBM
 
  Copyright IBM Corporation 2019, 2020. All Rights Reserved.

  US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure 
  restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
-->

<messages package="curam.message">
  <message name="HTTP_404_FILE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">No record found for the specified file. Please use a valid file ID and try again.</locale>
  </message>
  
    <message name="HTTP_404_API_NOT_ENABLED">
    <locale language="en">The requested API is not enabled. This API may be enabled by setting the corresponding property.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_CODETABLE_CODE_NOT_FOUND">
    <locale language="en">The specified code given for the documentTypeCode attribute does not exist. Please use a valid code from the DocumentType codetable and try again.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_NO_FILENAME">
    <locale language="en">No filename has been given in the file metadata custom header. It is mandatory to supply a value for the filename.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="ERR_NO_METADATA">
    <locale language="en">It is mandatory to send metadata in the specified custom request header, that contains the filename of the file. Other metadata attributes are optional.</locale>
  </message>
  
  <message name="HTTP_403_UNAUTHORIZED_ACCESS">
    <locale language="en">You are not authorized to access this file.</locale>
  </message>
  
 <message name="ERR_INVALID_FILE">
    <locale language="en">There is a problem with the contents of the file.</locale>
 </message>
 
 <message name="ERR_NO_FILE_CONTENTS">
    <locale language="en">The file does not exist or is an empty file with no content. Please specify a different file and try again.</locale>
 </message>
 
 <message name="ERR_EXTERNAL_FILE_REFERENCE">
    <locale language="en">The requested file does not store the contents of the file, it only stores a reference to a file located on another system. This API cannot be used to retrieve these details, however some File Location APIs are available for this purpose.</locale>
 </message>
 
  <message name="WARN_NO_FILE_VALIDATION_IMPLEMENTED">
    <locale language="en">"No implementation for file validation has been found, when uploading a file via a REST API. Unless file validation and virus scanning is handled elsewhere, the RESTFileValidationHook interface should be implemented."</locale>
 </message>
 
</messages>
